<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<News>
	<Version Major="3" Minor="6" Build="76" Revision="0"/>
	<Info Info="Version 3.6.76 is available.&#x0A;&#x0A;Improved object editor: objects can be dragged to groups, the content of a group is now displayed in the list, global objects and groups are now shown in bold.&#x0A;Reworked the window to select a condition or an action to be more simple and clear.&#x0A;Added the Event Store: Browse the events templates made by users from GDevApp.com, customize and insert them in your game. And double click on a template inserted in your game to edit it even after its insertion.&#x0A;Added Event Groups, that can be used to organize events.&#x0A;Added experimental support for Javascript events, for HTML5 games (see examples).&#x0A;Added support for saving (and loading) games to JSON files.&#x0A;New start page, and fixed bad alignment on Ubuntu.&#x0A;Fixed severe memory leaks when loading textures.&#x0A;Changed the middle click behavior: the middle button must be kept pressed to move in the scene editor.&#x0A;Platformer characters are pushed out of platforms if stuck inside.&#x0A;Added a Fill tool and Undo/Redo buttons in the editor of Tile Map objects.&#x0A;Various fixes and performance improvements for Tile Map objects.&#x0A;Added optional offset for the grid in the scene editor.&#x0A;Fixed bad cursor shown on Ubuntu in the scene editor.&#x0A;Fixed condition testing for the visibilty of a layer.&#x0A;Changed titles of some mouse related conditions to highlight the support of touchscreens.&#x0A;Added ScreenWidth and ScreenHeight expressions for HTML5 games.&#x0A;Fixed SceneWindowWidth and SceneWindowHeight for HTML5 games.&#x0A;Ensure that when multiple images are added to a sprite object on Ubuntu, the insertion is made in alphabetical order.&#x0A;Fixed syntax highlighting in the events editor.&#x0A;Various minor fixes and improvements.&#x0A;Switched from LGPL to MIT license for most codebase. Enjoy!" Lien="http://compilgames.net"/>
	<CommunityNews text="GDevApp is an online game creator based on GDevelop: Go try the most advanced game creation web app. Compatible with tablets and bundled with awesome graphics assets." link1="https://github.com/4ian/GD" linkLabel1="GDevelop on GitHub" link2="https://gdevapp.com?utm_source=software&amp;utm_medium=link_en&amp;utm_campaign=launch" linkLabel2="Try GDevApp, the online game creator based on GD"/>
</News>
