<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<News>
	<Version Major="4" Minor="0" Build="88" Revision="0"/>
	<Info Info="Version 4.0.88 is available.&#x0A;&#x0A;Huge internal changes to have multi-language support ('Unicode') in games.&#x0A;New AdMob object, that can be used to display ad banners (or interstitial screens) in HTML5 games exported to iOS/Android with Intel XDK.&#x0A;Automatisms are now called Behaviors for objects (more intuitive and easier to understand).&#x0A;New scene stacking feature: a new action allows to pause the current scene and launch a new one. You can then go back to the previous one with another action. This makes it easy to create a pause menu, a RPG combat system, rooms/building that you enter from a map...&#x0A;Improved export of HTML5 games to Cordova/Intel XDK.&#x0A;New editor for text objects&#x0A;Add 'Save as a folder project': projects can be saved with scenes, external events and external layouts stored in a different file for each. This makes it easier to collaborate on a game as a team.&#x0A;Hold Shift in scene editor to resize object while keeping its aspect ratio.&#x0A;Hold Shift in scene editor to rotate an object in increments.&#x0A;'Snap to grid' now snaps objects when resizing them in scene editor.&#x0A;Improvements on TileMap objects, including a reduced memory consumption for large maps.&#x0A;Improvements for HDPI ('retina') screens.&#x0A;Several bugfixes for pathfinding that should now work properly in all cases.&#x0A;Fixed search not working in the objects editor.&#x0A;Fixed extra border condition of Destroy Outside Behavior.&#x0A;New PIXI Particles advanced Javascript demo.&#x0A;Fixed objects from hidden layers could still be selected and moved in scene editor&#x0A;Internal code cleaning and improvements.&#x0A;Fixes for Mac OS X in the scene editor.&#x0A;Removed compilation of native games to a single file executable (was too unstable and prone to antivirus blocking).&#x0A;Add support for horizontal mouse wheel in the scene editor.&#x0A;Fixed Vertical Synchronization and framerate limit not applied after changing the window resolution in native games&#x0A;Fix small bug in Destroy Outside behavior of HTML5 games&#x0A;Add an option to repeat borders and center textures of PanelSprite objects for HTML5 games&#x0A;Improve performances of PanelSprite objects for HTML5 games&#x0A;Fix hitboxes collision condition for HTML5 games&#x0A;Fix conflicts when exporting a game using different images with the same file name.&#x0A;Fix error when deactivating a behavior of an object that was just created.&#x0A;Fix scene editor not properly refreshed after being resized on OS X." Lien="http://compilgames.net"/>
	<CommunityNews text="GDevelop has a new website! Help us to translate it to your language by going on the Crowdin project.&#x0A;&#x0A;GDevApp is an online game creator based on GDevelop: Go try the most advanced game creation web app. Compatible with tablets and bundled with awesome graphics assets." link1="https://crowdin.com/project/gdevelop-website/" linkLabel1="Help translate GD website" link2="https://gdevapp.com?utm_source=software&amp;utm_medium=link_en&amp;utm_campaign=launch" linkLabel2="Try GDevApp, the online game creator based on GD"/>
</News>
